



PROFILE

Dedicated IT Support Specialist with over 2 years of multifunctional experience with software, hardware, networks. Aiming to join a firm that values people and productivity and offers a great challenge to utilize my skills to improve end-user's experience.

EDUCATION

l	Dec 2017 – Jan 2020		
 	Diploma of Computer Network	Institute of Public Administration	GPA 4.69

EXPERIENCE

July 2020 – Present

IT Support Ram Health Care Group

- Respond to customer calls / tickets regarding hardware, software, and networking.
- Troubleshoot hardware, OS, Security, and Network Problems.
- Prepare and configure end-users' computers and peripherals.
- Guide users with simple, step-by-step instructions and conduct remote troubleshooting.
- Follow up with next-level support personnel.
- Help create technical documentation and manuals.
- Perform asset management and IT procurement activities.

Oct 2020 - Dec 2020

CO-OP Trainee	CTC / Saudi Aramco

Converting and Publishing eBooks

Supporting hardware and network devices.

COURSES

	CompTIA Network+ Course	Udemy
	CompTIA A+ / Security+ Course	IPA
٠	MCSA Guide to Installing and Configuring Microsoft Windows Server 2012 /R2	IPA
	Computer skills - Microsoft Office 2016	IAU
	Cyber security Course	Udemy
	Ethical hacking SQL Attack injection	Udemy
	HTML, CSS, jQuery and Bootstrap	Udemy
	Front End Web Development Course	Udemy

Future Seekers Program Misk Academy "Digital Marketing – Artificial Intelligence – Product Management - Business analytics"

SKILLS AND LANGUAGES

- Helpdesk Support
- Improving customer experience
- eBooks Publishing
- Adobe Photoshop
- HW/SW Installing
- Working with Microsoft Office
- Windows Client 10 and Server 12
 - English language ★★★★★

CERTIFICATIONS

Cisco Certified Network Associate - CCNA 200-125

Issue date Jan 2020